<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Englisher</title>
    <link>http://english.hengwong.fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Englisher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 12:13:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://english.hengwong.fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhinos taken back to Rwanda</title>
      <link>http://english.hengwong.fun/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://english.hengwong.fun/about/</guid>
      <description>This is where I learn English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhinos taken back to Rwanda</title>
      <link>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-7/rhinos-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-7/rhinos-1/</guid>
      <description>Rhinos taken back to Rwanda  The story… Rhinos taken back to Rwanda
Learn language related to… conservation
Need-to-know language Rhinos - 犀牛🦏
feeding time – period in which an animal or person is given food
keepers – professionals who take care of animals
released into the wild – set freeinto the natural environment
critically endangered – at high risk of extinction. 濒临灭绝的
Descendant of the animals - 后代</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primer: When You Have Too Much to Do</title>
      <link>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-6/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-6/post-1/</guid>
      <description>You have a to-do list that scrolls on for days. You are managing multiple projects, getting lots of email and messages on different messaging systems, managing finances and personal health habits and so much more.
It all keeps piling up, and it can feel overwhelming.
How do you keep up with it all? How do you find focus and peace and get stuff accomplished when you have too much on your plate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-7/wheather-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://english.hengwong.fun/posts/2019-7/wheather-2/</guid>
      <description>Weather words Words and pictures Weather, in meteorological terms, refers to the daily elements like temperature, wind and rain. In some countries the weather doesn&amp;rsquo;t change much from day to day. In others, the weather can change from season to season, day to day and even hour to hour.
Because the weather can change so much, some people keep an eye on the weather forecast so they can plan their daily activities - and decide what to wear!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>